Eduarda Candido de O e Silva

Head waitress

Cardiff CF5 2PQ eduardacandido236@gmail.com +44 7367 392121

Reliable, friendly and hardworking professional who quickly learns and masters new concepts and skills. Team leader with problem solving abilities and strong history of providing top-notch customer service, experienced in various areas.

Personal Details

Driver's License: None

Eligible to work in the UK: Yes

Highest Level of Education: GCSE or equivalent

Work Experience

Head Waitress

Corfu by Night - Cardiff November 2021 to Present

- Assist a team of hosts and hostesses by greeting, seating, and thanking customers.
- Answer questions about the menu and make recommendations when appropriate or requested.
- Take orders from and serve food and beverages to customers.
- Check in with guests to ensure they are happy and taking action to correct any issues they may be experiencing.
- Trained incoming staff regarding the restaurant's procedures, culture and practices.
- Surpervised floor staff to ensure that guests are served promptly and courteously to properly reflect the environment and standards of the restaurant.

Sales Account Manager

BSP Business Group - Birmingham April 2021 to November 2021

- Representing clients on their behalf.
- Delivering high quality customer service.
- Helping customers with registration process and clarifying concerns.
- Coaching and training people, and taking on responsibilities.
- Using, learning and teaching sales systems in a daily basis.
- Got promoted to Account Manager 3 weeks after starting the role.
- Got selected to be part of an expansion in Cardiff.

Warehouse Worker

Central Mailing Services LTD - Birmingham August 2020 to March 2021

- Performed production duties such as manual lifting, packaging, taping, labeling and sorting.
- Attached stickers, packed boxes, cleaned and checked product for quality assurance.
- Responsible for sorting mail in the right place. Bundled, labeled, and routed sorted mail to designated areas.
- Production and quality focused, worked in continuous, demanding, high volume production environment.

Packer

Colorway Advertising - Birmingham August 2020 to December 2020

- Verified all orders and ensured all product meets customers specifications.
- Scanned orders and printing shipping labels.
- Inspected, labeled and packed product for shipment.
- Training of employees new to the department.
- Ensured that company was satisfied with my work, by working hard, fast, and effectively.
- Work proficiently both as a part of a team and individually in a self-motivated environment with little supervision.

Line Packer

Cobrey Farms - Ross-on-Wye April 2020 to July 2020

- · Assigned and marked items with grades and official acceptance or rejection status.
- Mentored new employees on daily warehouse procedures and answered task-related questions for quick job acclimation.
- Sorted and weighed products before packing, ensuring products stayed at required specifications and company standards.
- · Maintained safe workplaces by keeping spaces clean, organised and hazard-free.

Barista and Waitress

Maria's Kitchen - London February 2020 to April 2020

- Served guests promptly to ensure food remained at proper temperatures.
- Greeting, seating, taking orders, serving and thanking customers.
- Cleaned table linens, table settings, glassware, windowsills, carpets, counters, floors, storage areas and service refrigerators.
- Delivered exceptional, friendly and fast service.
- Prepared and served hot and cold beverages such as coffees, espresso drinks, blended coffees and teas.

Barista/Cashier

Grab a Bite - London July 2019 to December 2019

- Completed opening, closing and shift change tasks in full to promote store efficiency.
- Maintained excellent standards of service through impeccable attention to detail.
- Consistently maintained high levels of cleanliness, organization, storage, and sanitation of food and beverage products to ensure quality.
- Trained workers, including food preparation, money handling and cleaning roles.

Education

GCSE or equivalent

Skills

- Teamwork and collaboration
- Professional and friendly
- Problem-solving abilities
- Customer service
- Fast learning
- Direct sales
- Account Management
- Communication skills
- Hospitality
- IT
- IT
- IT
- Time management
- Computer skills
- IT
- Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft Powerpoint

Languages

- Portuguese Expert
- Spanish Intermediate
- Greek Beginner